<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RashanStore</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>


    <string name="order_id">Order Id : </string>
    <string name="customer_id">Customer Id : </string>
    <string name="transaction_amount">Transaction Amount : </string>
    <string name="channel_id">Channel Id : </string>
    <string name="industry_type_id">Industry Type Id : </string>
    <string name="website">Website : </string>
    <string name="theme">Theme : </string>
    <string name="cust_email_id">Email Id : </string>
    <string name="cust_mobile_no">Mobile Number : </string>
    <string name="merchant_id">Merchant Id : </string>
    <string name="checksum_generation_url">Checksum Generation URL : </string>
    <string name="checksum_verification_url">Checksum Verification URL : </string>
    <string name="start_transaction">Start Transaction</string>
    <string name="sample_order_id">ORDER</string>
    <string name="sample_customer_id">CUST23657</string>
    <string name="sample_transaction_amount">1</string>
    <string name="sample_channel_id">WAP</string>
    <string name="sample_industry_type_id">Retail</string>
    <string name="sample_website">worldpressplg</string>
    <string name="sample_theme">merchant</string>
    <string name="sample_cust_email_id">abc@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="sample_cust_mobile_no">123</string>
    <string name="sample_merchant_id_staging">WorldP64425807474247</string>
    <string name="sample_checksum_generation_url">https://pguat.paytm.com/merchant-chksum/ChecksumGenerator</string>
    <string name="sample_checksum_verification_url">https://pguat.paytm.com/merchant-chksum/ValidateChksum</string>
    <string name="title_activity_navigation">navigation</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>

    <string name="content_about">We Are To Start The New Era That Will Pronounce A Story of Your Comfort, Your Routine, Your Necessities And Our Service To Fulfill All These.\n\n
I, Rashan Stores. Our Motive " nai aana lene, hum aayenge dene” . We Deal With Your Shops and Kitchen. We Will Be Your Warehouse.\n
Our Initiative, Two Steps Service To Bring The Whole Market In Your Hand.\n
Step 1 : Think.\n
Step 2 : Post or Add Your Products.\n
You Are Done, Now Its Our Turn..\n
We Will Deliver Excellence, Perfection, Purity And Quality; At Your Time, At Your Place.\n
Countdown ticking...</string>
    <string name="content_terms1">
    By availing the Logistics Services and/ or Payment Services (defined below) of Hiveloop Logistics Private Limited (hereinafter referred to as ‘we’/ ‘us’), Buyer or Seller or any other party acting on their behalf (hereinafter collectively referred to as ‘you’) with an interest in the Order(s) (defined below) agree to be bound by the terms and conditions set out herein below ("Terms”).\n
    I.	Definitions:\n
    In these Terms:
    a.	"Buyer(s)” shall mean the person or individual who has purchased the Products offered for sale by the Sellers on the Platform and is availing Logistics Services and Payment Services from us.\n\n
    b.	"Chargeback” is a settled transaction that is reversed to the Buyer(s) by the Payment Instruments, upon receiving a chargeback request from the Buyer(s), upon failure of the Seller(s) to provide an explanation along with documentary evidence that the chargeback request should be rejected.\n\n
    c.	‘Consignee’ shall mean the Buyer or any person named in the Delivery Note or any of his/her representatives that takes the delivery of Shipment being transported.\n\n
    d.	‘Dangerous Goods’ includes products that are or may become of a dangerous, hazardous, inflammable, radioactive, or damaging nature, products liable to taint or affect other products and products likely to harbor or encourage vermin or other pests.\n\n
    e.	‘Delivery Note’ shall means the Waybill containing the essential information (as determined by us on our sole discretion) required for the performance of the Logistics Services, including name, delivery address and contact number (if applicable) of the Consignee or the designated recipient of the Shipment, description of the contents of the Shipment (if applicable) and COD details (if applicable).\n\n
    f.	‘Logistics Services’ means the shipping, delivery, including cash on delivery ("COD”) services and other services provided by us to you pursuant to these Terms.\n\n
    g.	"Order(s)” shall mean an order placed by the Buyer(s) for purchase of Products prescribed by the Seller(s) of such Products. Each Order shall be specifically designated by a unique order number.\n\n
    h.	"Order Detail(s)” shall mean the details relating to the Order including without limitation, the description of Products, cost of the Products, total amount payable, delivery date etc.\n\n
    i.	"Payment Services” shall mean the collection of payments by us, for the Order(s), from the Buyer(s): (i) using Payment Instruments (defined below), various banks or financial institutions, that enables the Buyer(s) to pay online; and/ or (ii) for cash on delivery Order(s), by collecting cash and remitting the same to the Seller(s) of Products.\n\n
    j.	‘Platform’ means the any website and/ or mobile application whereby Seller(s) display/ list and sell their Products.\n\n
    k.	"Product(s)” shall mean multiple categories of goods including but not limited to mobiles, cameras, computers, apparels, footwear, healthcare and personal products, consumer home appliances and consumer electronics etc.\n\n
    l.	"Seller(s)” shall mean the sellers/ vendors that list/ offer for sale to Buyers their Products through the Platform in accordance with the terms of use of such Platform.\n\n
    m.	"Shipment(s) / Consignment(s) means all Products (excluding documents) that travel under one Delivery Note and which may be carried by any means we choose in our discretion, including air, road or any other carrier.\n\n
    n.	\'Waybill\' shall include any label that may be produced by us under automated systems, air waybill, or consignment note which shall incorporate these Terms.\n\n

    II.	If you are availing the Logistics Services from us, you agree to be bound by the following terms and conditions:\n\n
    1.	Conditions to Provision of Logistics Services:\n\n
    a.	We, in our sole discretion, reserve the right to refuse the delivery of any Shipment and/ or forfeit delivery of any Shipment without any liability thereof.\n\n
    b.	We are entitled to select third party sub-contractors (including but not limited to carriers, storage keepers, warehousing agents, stuffing agents, packers, surveyors, transporters) as independent agents for performance of the Logistics Services under these Terms and Conditions.\n\n
    c.	Consignments which contain Dangerous Goods or such goods that are expressly prohibited by the railway/airport authority or any other transport agency or government authority or any other law or regulation that may be applicable, shall not be accepted by us for delivery.\n\n
    d.	Consignments addressed to a post box number or with incomplete address will not be delivered by us and the same will be rejected by us.\n\n
    e.	We may, in our sole discretion, reject any Shipment for the provision of Logistics Services and shall return such rejected Shipment in accordance with the relevant return policy that may be notified by us, from time to time.\n\n
    f.	We reserve our right to weigh the Shipment at our own weighing centers and in the event of any discrepancy, additional charges may be levied on the Shipment. Any decision by us with respect to any inaccuracy in the information or discrepancy in weight shall be final and you hereby authorize us to determine the accurate weight on your behalf.\n\n
    g.	We shall not be liable for any loss arising due to confiscation of Shipments by any government agencies due to lack of proper documents or inaccurate information provided to us.\n\n
    2.	Representation, warranties, and obligations :\n\n
    a.	Seller shall ensure that the Consignment does not contain any letter of communication which will infringe the Indian Postal Act, 1983 or any other applicable laws. We accept Consignments in good faith that the Consignments do not contain anything which will infringe or be in violation of any applicable laws.\n\n
    b.	If more than one Consignment is booked to the same receiver, Seller must ensure that the full address of the Consignee or designated recipient is written on all the Consignments.\n\n
    c.	Seller shall not enclose cash, high value gift articles, share certificates, travel documents, Dangerous Goods, explosives, firearms, cattle, or any other product that is prohibited by applicable laws in the Shipment. If Dangerous Goods or any goods that are prohibited by applicable laws are found in the Shipment which constitute a risk to other goods, property, life or health, such Shipment may without notice be destroyed or otherwise dealt with at our sole discretion and at your risk and expense. In this regard you shall, at all times, fully indemnify us and hold us harmless against all penalties, claims, damages, losses, costs and expenses (including but not limited to legal expenses) whatsoever arising in connection with any such goods.\n\n
    d.	Seller shall be solely responsible to declare the accurate value of the Consignment in the consignment note at the time of booking your Consignment for delivery.\n\n
    e.	Seller represents and warrants that the description and particulars of the Consignment (including but not limited to the weight, content, measure, quality, condition, marks, numbers, and value) are complete and accurate with all laws, regulations, and requirements that may be applicable.\n\n
    f.	Seller represents and warrants that:\n\n
    i.	all information provided by you or person acting on your behalf relating to the Shipment(s) are complete and accurate;\n\n
    ii.	the Shipment(s) are properly and sufficiently prepared, packed, stowed, labelled, and/or marked;\n\n
    iii.	the Shipment(s) are packed in a manner adequate to withstand normal handling or storing while transporting; and/or\n\n
    iv.	the Shipment(s) are in compliance with all laws, regulations, and requirements as may be applicable.\n\n
    g.	Seller shall ensure that all the Consignments are provided to us before the specified cut-off-time specified by us for on time delivery with all the proper documents (in accordance with applicable laws including but not limited to goods and services tax Act, 2007 (GST)) required to ship the Shipments. GST on the products contained in Shipments and all applicable statutory tax compliances shall be your sole responsibility and we shall not be responsible for any losses, damages resulting from any such non-compliances.\n\n
    h.	Seller shall be solely responsible to ensure that the Consignment is handed over to us within the time slots allotted to Seller by us. If Seller does not handover the Shipment within the time slot allotted, then Seller shall be charged extra for second attempt being made by us to take the Shipment.\n\n
    i.	Seller shall be solely responsible for procuring appropriate insurance policies for the Consignments to cover all or any risks and liabilities that Seller may foresee. If Seller requires greater protection, then insurance cover may be arranged by us for the Shipment, in our sole discretion, upon your prior written instructions.\n\n
    3.	Delivery Services:\n\n
    a.	Upon receiving a service order for the Logistics Services, we shall use our best endeavours to deliver the Shipment(s) to the delivery address and designated recipient in the Delivery Note. For the avoidance of doubt, the designated recipient may not be the Consignee. We will endeavor to verify the identification of the person receiving the Package at the designated delivery address and obtain the signature of such person’s signature on the Delivery Note.\n\n
    b.	For onward delivery of Shipments, Seller hereby authorizes us to print Delivery Note containing information with respect to Shipment on its behalf.\n\n
    c.	Shipments shall be delivered on ‘as is’ basis and unless agreed otherwise, we are under no obligation to inspect the contents of the Shipment. However, we may, in our sole discretion, at any time and without notice to Seller, inspect the contents of Shipment to ensure Seller’s compliance to these Terms.\n\n
    d.	Proof of delivery of the Shipment can be made available upon Seller’s request provided such a request is made within 30 days from the date of dispatch of the Consignment. We will not accede to any requests after the expiry of the aforesaid time limit.\n\n
    e.	Every effort will be made to adhere to the delivery schedule, that may be prescribed by Seller, however, the Shipment may be delayed due to circumstances beyond our reasonable control.\n\n
    f.	If the performance of our obligations, in our reasonable opinion is or is likely to be affected by any hindrance, risk, delay, difficulty, or disadvantage whatsoever and which cannot be avoided by our reasonable endeavors, we may, on giving notice in writing to you or without notice where it is not reasonably possible to give such notice, treat the performance of the obligations as terminated and place the Shipment or any part of them at your disposal at any place which the we may deem safe and convenient, whereupon our responsibility in respect of the Shipment shall cease. Seller shall be responsible for any additional costs of carriage to, and delivery and storage at, such place and all other expenses incurred by us in this regard.\n\n
    4.	Failed Delivery:\n\n
    a.	You acknowledge that a delivery failure ("Failed Delivery”) may occur for various reasons, including but not limited to:\n\n
    i.	the Consignee’s name is incorrectly stated in the Delivery Note;\n\n
    ii.	the delivery address is incorrectly stated in the Delivery Note;\n\n
    iii.	there is no recipient available at the designated delivery address to receive the Shipment; or\n\n
    iv.	the recipient refuses to receive the Shipment.\n\n
    b.	In the event of a Failed Delivery due to the reasons stated in clause (a) above, we shall retain the Shipment and make a reasonable number of re-delivery attempts (as determined by us in our sole discretion) to deliver the Shipment.\n\n
    c.	In the event of Failed Delivery even after making such number of re-delivery attempts to deliver the Shipment, we will notify Seller and use reasonable efforts to return the Shipment to Seller in accordance with our internal policies.\n\n
    d.	If the Consignee does not take delivery of the Shipment or any part thereof, we shall be entitled, without further notice, to store the Shipment or any part of the Shipment at your sole risk and expense. Such storage shall constitute delivery of the Shipment and our liability shall wholly cease.\n\n
    5.	Returns:\n\n
    a.	We will notify Seller of any returned Shipment and shall use our reasonable efforts to return the Shipment to Seller in accordance with our internal policies. However, if Seller fails to notify the return delivery address within the period stated in our written intimation we may, in our sole discretion, release, dispose of or sell the Shipment or any of its content without incurring any liability or payment obligation whatsoever to Seller or Buyer.\n\n
    b.	Notwithstanding anything contained under these Terms, any costs that may be incurred by us in connection of the delivery of the returned Shipment to the Seller, including without limitation the processing fees, shipping fees, and any applicable duties and taxes, shall be borne by Seller.\n\n
    6.	COD Services for Buyers:\n\n
    a.	Seller hereby authorizes us to perform COD services and collect the cash on your behalf from the Buyer and the collected COD shall be settled and remitted to Seller’s account in accordance with the settlement process as set out in the terms for Payment Services as set out hereinbelow and Seller hereby agrees to be bound by the provisions of the terms for Payment Services in this regard.\n\n
    b.	Seller acknowledges and agrees that in performing the COD Services, we are acting merely as a payment collection agent and shall take no responsibility as to the legality of any payment transaction between the Seller and the Consignee.\n\n
    7.	Express Remittance Facility for Sellers:\n\n
    In the event Seller(s) request for payment for the Order(s) at the time of handing over Shipment to us for onward delivery of Consignment to the Consignee, we may in our sole and absolute discretion, pay to the Seller(s) such percentage of the amount of Shipment being handed over to us. Further, in the event the Buyer refuses to accept the Products we will return the Shipment to the Seller and the Seller shall be liable to return to us the money received by Seller from us in the form of express remittance. If the Buyer has accepted the Shipment, the money paid by the Buyer shall be adjusted corresponding to the amount of express remittance paid to the Seller.\n\n
    8.	Indemnity:\n\n
    You agree to indemnify, defend and hold harmless us, our affiliates and their related officers, directors, employees, agents and sub-contractors from and against all liability, loss, claims (including claims from third parties, sub-contractors or agents), damages, awards, penalties (including penalties imposed by government or regulatory authorities) or expenses (including attorney’s fees) arising out of or related to:\n\n
    a.	any breach of your obligations, representations or warranties under these Terms;\n\n
    b.	any claim or action by a third party in connection with any defect in title of any products;\n\n
    c.	information (whether to us or our affiliates, or their sub-contractors, agents or service providers, or government or regulatory authorities) in relation to the Shipment or otherwise pursuant to these Terms or in contemplation of the Logistics Services, that is incorrect, misleading, or erroneous;\n\n
    d.	your omission to provide information or documentation required by us or any government or regulatory authorities;\n\n
    e.	any alleged or actual patent, copyright, trade secret, trademark, trade name, or other intellectual property right infringement or other claim, demand or action resulting from the advertising, publishing, promotion, manufacture, sale, distribution or use of any of the products;\n\n
    f.	any alleged or actual personal injury, death or property damage suffered by any party arising from the supply or sale of the Shipment to that party;\n\n
    g.	any claim by a third party or Consignee made pursuant to, or liability arising under any consumer protection laws, including any non-conformity or defect in, or any recall of, any of products.\n\n
    9.	Limitation of Liability:\n\n
    In no event will we be liable for indirect, incidental, special or consequential damages, including loss of use, loss of profits or interruption of business, howsoever caused or on any theory of liability. We shall not have any liability whatsoever for any claims arising from: (a) any of your acts or omissions; (b) compliance with the instructions given by you or any person acting on your behalf; (c) an act or order of any government authority; (d) the insufficiency of the packing or labelling of Shipment; (e) the nature or description of the Shipment; (f) riots, civil commotions, strikes, lockouts, stoppage or restraint of labour; (g) explosion, fire, flood or storm; (h) any cause which we could not avoid and the consequences whereof we could not prevent by the exercise of reasonable diligence; (i) any loss, miss-delivery, delay or damage to any Shipment; and/or (j) any dispute or claims between the Seller and the Consignee/ Buyer including without limitation relating to the Shipment or Products hereunder.\n\n
    Our aggregate liability (inclusive of interest and legal and other costs) arising under or in connection with the Logistics Services (whether by reason of any negligence or any non-fraudulent misrepresentation, any breach of contract or any express or implied warranty, condition or term of these Terms or any duty at common law) will not in any way exceed an amount of INR 5000/-.\n\n
    10.	Taxes:\n\n
    a.	We shall charge the Buyer for providing Logistics Services and unless otherwise stated, all such charges shall be exclusive of Goods and Service Tax. The charges payable for availing the Logistics Services will be displayed in the Rate Card section of the Platform and the same may be modified or amended, from time to time, solely in our discretion without any notice thereof. It shall be Buyer’s duty to routinely check on such charges. In the event you continue to avail the Logistics Services from us, it shall be deemed that you have agreed to such change in charges.\n\n
    b.	Octroi or any other charges levied by any central/state/local authorities wherever applicable shall be extra and Buyer shall be liable to pay the same.\n\n
    11.	Lien:\n\n
    We shall have a general and particular lien on the goods and other contents of Shipments  and all documents relating thereto in an event of the default by you in the payment of sums of whatever nature due and payable by you to us including, without limitation, charge for attending, co-operating, reporting, fumigating, devanning, restoring, storing or reconditioning and/or all expenses incurred for the benefit or protection of the Shipments, and also for any payments, duties, fines or other expenses including but not limited to interest and legal costs and expenses, due at any time to us from you. If any amount due and payable by you to us is not paid, upon the giving of fifteen (15) calendar days prior written notice, we may, at our absolute discretion and without notice, suspend or cease providing all or any part of the Logistics Services without any liability whatsoever to you or any third party and, at our absolute discretion, may proceed to sell the Shipments by way of public auction or private tender without further notice. Our rights are reserved for any shortfall subsequent to the disposal of the Shipments.\n\n
</string>
    <string name="content_terms2">If you are availing the Payment Services from us, you agree to be bound by the following terms and conditions:\n\n
    0.	Payment Services:\n\n
    a.	In order to facilitate the purchase of Products by Buyer(s), we have entered into arrangements with various third-party payment providers such as pre-paid cash cards, wallets, banks, or financial institutions and such other entities ("Payment Instrument(s)") as may be determined by us, in our sole discretion, which shall enable the Buyer(s) to pay for the Orders placed by the Buyer(s) on the Platform.\n\n
    b.	Buyer(s) hereby agrees and acknowledges that we shall collect the payment, for the Orders placed by the Buyer(s), on behalf of the Seller. By availing the Payment Services, Buyer(s) authorizes us and our authorized representatives to collect the transaction amount payable for an Order from the Buyer(s), on behalf of the Seller, and process, facilitate and remit the payments to the Seller.\n\n
    c.	Upon placement of Order on Platform, Buyer(s) shall be able to make payment for the Order placed by the Buyer(s) for completing the transaction through one of the Payment Instruments or methods of payment prescribed by us and made available, from time to time, on the Platform.\n\n
    d.	Buyer(s) hereby acknowledges that the Buyer(s) is solely responsible for the transactions / payments made to the Seller for the Products purchased by the Buyer(s). Buyer(s) hereby acknowledges that we do not have any obligation, responsibility or liability to verify any transactions authenticated and/or authorised by the Buyer(s) or its payment instructions.\n\n
    e.	We do not make any representations pertaining to the information, content, Products included on or delivery of the Products or otherwise made available to Buyer(s) and Buyer(s) acknowledges that we are only acting as an intermediary between the Buyer(s) and the Seller. Buyer(s) hereby further agrees, acknowledges and confirms that we are not responsible in any way for the Products purchased by the Buyer(s) from the Seller and it is explicitly agreed by Buyer(s) that we will not in any way, under any circumstances whatsoever, be responsible or held liable for Products purchased by Buyer(s) from the Seller and/or in relation to any issue and/or dispute thereof. Buyer(s) hereby further agrees, acknowledges and confirms that under the aforesaid circumstances Buyer’s only recourse will be against the Seller and we will not be made a party to any such issue and/or dispute between the Buyer(s) and the Seller.\n\n
    f.	We shall have the right to block your access to the Payment Services, if we in our sole discretion determine that the transaction being undertaken by you is not genuine or suspicious or fraudulent.\n\n
    g.	Buyer(s) hereby consents and agrees to comply with guidelines, instructions, requests, etc., as maybe made by us or third party banks or financial institutions, as the case may be or a payment system provider or Payment Instrument from time to time, in relation to these Payment Services.\n\n
    h.	Buyer(s) hereby acknowledges and agrees that we shall not be liable for failure of any transaction undertaken on Platform for any reason whatsoever including but not limited to non-performance or omission or commission on the part of the Seller, deficiency of service and/or Products delivered, technical errors on the Platform. Buyer(s) further acknowledges that we shall not be responsible, in any manner whatsoever, for any loss incurred by the Buyer(s) for a failed / incomplete transaction undertaken by the Buyer(s) using these Payment Services.\n\n
    1.	Submission of Personal Information:\n\n
    a.	You agree that the personal information including without limitation name, address, contact number, credit card details ("Personal Information") that you provide on the Platform upon registration shall be made available to us by Platform operator at the time of your availing the Payment Services. You represent and warrant that, at all times, this Personal Information will be true, accurate, current and complete.\n\n
    b.	You agree to maintain and update the Personal Information in case of any change and shall ensure that the Personal Information provided by you is true, accurate and complete.\n\n
    c.	It is hereby clarified that we shall not be liable in any manner whatsoever for any loss or damage incurred by you or any dispute initiated by or against you, due any untrue, inaccurate, not current or incomplete Personal Information provided to us.\n\n
    d.	You hereby agree, acknowledge and accept that we shall use your Personal Information in accordance with our Privacy Policy.\n\n
    2.	Cancellation and Refunds:\n\n
    We hereby undertake and agree, that in the event of a cancellation/refund request being made by the Buyer(s) or the Seller in accordance with our internal policies, the refunded transaction amount (less cancellation charges, if any) ("Refund Amount") shall be credited to the Buyer(s)’s account. All refunds shall be processed in the same manner as they are received. Refund Amount will reflect in the Buyer’s account based on respective banks policies.\n\n
    3.	Limitation of Liability:\n\n
    a.	You acknowledge that our liability with respect to the Payment Services shall be limited and shall be as per these terms and conditions.\n\n
    b.	You acknowledge that the Payment Services are being provided on a ‘as is’ and ‘as available’ basis and may be interrupted while browsing, transacting, using or uploading information on the Platform. You further agree that we reserve the right to suspend the Payment Services, forthwith without assigning any reason whatsoever, at our sole discretion.\n\n
    c.	You agree and confirm that the Payment Services are being provided to you on a best efforts basis with all efforts to keep these valid and subsisting. We shall not in any manner be liable to you for failure or delay in providing the Payment Services.\n\n
    d.	You assume the entire risk of using the Payment Services, to the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, in no event shall we be liable to you for any special, incidental, indirect, punitive or consequential damages whatsoever (including, without limitation, damages of loss of goods or services, loss of business profits, business interruption, loss of information, or any other pecuniary loss) arising out of the use of, or inability to use or access of the Payment Services or for any security breach or any virus, bug, unauthorised intervention, defect, or technical malfunctioning of the website, whether or not foreseeable and whether or not we have been advised of the possibility of such damages, or based on any theory of liability, including breach of contract or warranty, negligence or other tortious action, or any other claim arising out, of or in connection with, your use of, or access to, the Payment Services. Further, we shall not be liable to you for any temporary disablement, permanent discontinuance of the Payment Services by us or for any consequences resulting from such actions.\n\n
    e.	Our aggregate liability (inclusive of interest and legal and other costs) arising under or in connection with Payment Services (whether by reason of any negligence or any non-fraudulent misrepresentation, any breach of contract or any express or implied warranty, condition or term of these Terms or any duty at common law) will not in any way exceed an amount of INR 1000/-.\n\n
    4.	Settlements:\n\n
    a.	We will transmit the payments for the Orders received from the Buyer(s) and payable to the Seller from our nodal account to the Seller’s designated bank account, within 3 (three) bank working days (or such other period as may be prescribed by the Reserve Bank of India from time to time) from completion of transaction i.e. from the date of delivery of the Order to the Buyer(s). Seller will receive the amount (minus our fee (if any)) in their bank account within ‘T+3’ bank working days where ‘T’ is the date of delivery of the Order to the Buyer(s).\n\n
    b.	We shall be entitled to recover from the Seller, from time to time, any amounts due from it or incurred by us on account of the following, unless the same are caused on account of negligence, act or omission of our or its employees, officers etc.:\n\n
    A.	Chargeback of transactions;\n\n
    B.	Any penalty or charge which may be levied on us by the Payment Instruments or the clearing house i.e. Reserve Bank of India or its local clearing agent (as the case may be) arising, inter alia, for:\n\n
    i.	excessive Chargeback of transactions or excessive failure of transactions or excessive buyer disputes and/or any other reason;\n\n
    ii.	any amount due to us from the Sellers.\n\n
    If there are reasonable grounds to suspect that a transaction has been conducted in breach of any applicable laws or is a fraudulent transaction, Payment Instruments shall be entitled to suspend or withhold the payments of the Seller that are due to the Seller, pending enquiries by the Payment Instruments and till the resolution of such issues.\n\n
    If any of the issues stated in this clause are caused by or on behalf of Seller, Seller shall indemnify and hold us harmless against any such claims made by the Payment Instruments, or the Buyer(s), as the case may be.\n\n
    In case of an occurrence of a Chargeback event, we reserve our right to withhold the settlements to the Sellers, pending enquiries by the Payment Instruments or any regulatory body, as the case may be, till the resolution of such issues.\n\n

    Miscellaneous Clauses:\n\n
    .	We shall not be liable for any loss arising due to the causes beyond our control including without limitation, act of god, floods, accidents, fire, theft, war or any other force majeure event.\n\n
    a.	All matters of business should be settled exclusively within the jurisdiction of the Bangalore, Karnataka and shall be subject to exclusive jurisdiction of courts at Bangalore, Karnataka.\n\n
    b.	These Terms shall not be assigned by you without our prior written consent. Any purported transfer, assignment, or delegation without such prior written consent shall be null and void. We may assign or transfer these Terms for any reason to any person. Subject to the foregoing, these Terms shall bind and inure to the benefit of each party’s successors and permitted assigns.\n\n
    c.	By availing the Logistics Services and Payment Services, you acknowledge and agree to be bound by our Privacy Policy. You further agree and accept that we may use your personal information or any personal information that may be provided by you for the purposes of providing Logistics Services and Payment Services in accordance with the privacy policy. You will immediately notify us if you become aware of or suspects any unauthorized use or access to the user data and shall co-operate with us in investigation of such breach and the mitigation of any damage.\n\n
    d.	We may modify these Terms from time to time, and any such changes will be reflected on the Platform and be effective immediately upon the changes being reflected on the Platform. You agree to be bound to any such changes or modifications and understand and accept the importance of regularly reviewing these Terms as updated on the Platform.\n\n
    e.	The relationship between you and us is one of independent contractors, and nothing contained in these Terms will be construed to (i) give either party the power to direct and control the day-to-day activities of the other, (ii) constitute the parties as partners, joint ventures, co-owners or otherwise as participants in a joint or common undertaking, or (iii) allow you to create or assume any obligation on our behalf for any purpose whatsoever.\n\n
    f.	The invalidity or unenforceability of any provision shall not affect any other part of these Terms. These Terms read along with the Privacy Policy shall constitute the entire understanding between the parties hereto and all other agreements, understanding, acknowledgments shall be stand superseded.\n\n
    g.	These Terms shall not be assigned by you without our prior written consent. Any purported transfer, assignment, or delegation without such prior written consent shall be null and void. We may assign or transfer these Terms for any reason to any person. Subject to the foregoing, these Terms shall bind and inure to the benefit of each party’s successors and permitted assigns.\n\n
         </string>
    <string name="content_terms3">
    Editorial\n\n
    LOGIN\n\n
    •
    TERMS OF USE\n\n
    These Terms of Use describe the terms and conditions applicable to your access and use of the platform www.RashanStore.in and its mobile application platform (each a "Platform”).  This document is a legally binding agreement between you as the user(s) of the Platform (referred to as "you”, "your” or "User” hereinafter) and the Hiveloop Technology Private Limited entity listed in clause 2.a below (referred to as "we”, "our” or "Rashan Store” hereinafter).\n\n
    1.	Application and Acceptance of the Terms\n\n
    a.	User’s use of the Platform and Rashan Store’s services, software and products (collectively the as the "Services” hereinafter) is subject to the terms and conditions contained in this document as well as the Privacy Policy, The Product Listing Policy, IP Infringement Policy and any other rules and policies of the Platform that Rashan Store may publish from time to time.\n\n
    b.	This document and such other rules and policies of the Platform are collectively referred to below as the "Terms”.  By accessing the Platform or using the Services, User agrees to accept and be bound by the Terms.  Please do not use the Services or access the Platform if you do not accept all of the Terms or are unable to be bound by the Terms.\n\n
    c.	User may not use the Services and may not accept the Terms if you are not of legal age to form a binding contract with Rashan Store.\n\n
    d.	You acknowledge and agree that Rashan Store may amend any Terms at any time by posting the relevant amended and restated Terms on the Platform.  By continuing to use the Services or the Platform, you acknowledge to have accepted the amended Terms and agree that the amended Terms will apply to you.\n\n
    e.	The Terms may not otherwise be modified except in writing by an authorized officer of Rashan Store.\n\n

    2.	Provision of Services\n\n
    a.	The Rashan Store contracting entity that you are contracting with for access to the Platform is Hiveloop Technology Private Limited. In case you avail services while accessing the Platform, that may be supported and/or provided by third party service provider(s), for all such services your contracting entity will be such third party service provider(s), as the case may be. Rashan Store disclaims all liability for any claims that may arise pursuant to your use of services provided by such affiliates of third party service provider(s).\n\n
    b.	You must register as a member on the Platform in order to access and use Services. Further, Rashan Store reserves the right, without prior notice, to restrict access to or use of certain Services (or any features within the Services) subject to other conditions that Rashan Store may impose in its discretion.\n\n

    3.	Users Generally\n\n
    a.	You agree to use the Platform or Services solely for your own private and internal purposes. You agree that (a) you will not copy, reproduce, download, re-publish, sell, distribute or resell any Services or any information, text, images, graphics, video clips, sound, directories, files, databases or listings, etc. available on or through the Platform (the "Site Content”), and (b) you will not copy, reproduce, download, compile or otherwise use any Platform Content for the purposes of operating a business that competes with Rashan Store, or otherwise commercially exploiting the Platform Content or systematic retrieval of Platform Content from the Platform to create or compile, directly or indirectly, a collection, compilation, database or directory (whether through robots, spiders, automatic devices or manual processes).\n\n
    b.	You must read Rashan Store’s Privacy Policy which governs the protection and use of personal information about Users of Platform. You accept the terms of the Privacy Policy and agree to the use of the personal information about you in accordance with the Privacy Policy.\n\n
    c.	Rashan Store may allow Users access to content, products or services offered by third parties through hyperlinks (in the form of word link, banners, channels or otherwise), API or otherwise to such third parties\' web sites. You are cautioned to read such third parties terms and conditions and/or privacy policies before using the Platform with respect to such content, products or services that you may avail. You acknowledge that Rashan Store has no control over such third parties\' web sites and shall not be responsible or liable to anyone for such web sites, or any content, products or services made available on such web sites.\n\n
    d.	You agree not to undertake any action which may undermine the integrity of Rashan Store’s feedback system.\n\n
    e.	By posting or displaying any information, content or material ("User Content") on the Platform or providing any User Content to Rashan Store or our representative(s), you grant an irrevocable, perpetual, worldwide, royalty-free, and sub-licensable license to Rashan Store to display, transmit, distribute, reproduce, publish, duplicate, adapt, modify, translate, create derivative works, and otherwise use any or all of the User Content in any form, media, or technology now known or not currently known in any manner and for any purpose which may be beneficial to the operation of the Platform, the provision of any Services and/or the business of the User. You confirm and warrant to Rashan Store that you have all the rights, power and authority necessary to grant the above license.\n\n
    f.	User agree, undertake and confirm that User’s use of Platform shall be strictly governed by the following binding principles:\n\n
    i.	User shall not host, display, upload, modify, publish, transmit, update or share any information which:\n\n
    1.	belongs to another person and to which User does not have any right to;\n\n
    2.	is grossly harmful, harassing, blasphemous, defamatory, obscene, pornographic, paedophilic, libellous, invasive of others privacy, hateful, or racially, ethnically objectionable, disparaging, relating or encouraging money laundering or gambling, or otherwise unlawful in any manner whatever; or unlawfully threatening or unlawfully harassing including but not limited to "indecent representation of women" within the meaning of the Indecent Representation of Women (Prohibition) Act, 1986;\n\n
    3.	is misleading in any way;\n\n
    4.	is patently offensive to the online community, such as sexually explicit content, or content that promotes obscenity, paedophilia, racism, bigotry, hatred or physical harm of any kind against any group or individual;\n\n
    5.	harasses or advocates harassment of another person;\n\n
    6.	involves the transmission of "junk mail", "chain letters", or unsolicited mass mailing or "spamming" or messages using Rashan Store communication platform;\n\n
    7.	promotes illegal activities or conduct that is abusive, threatening, obscene, defamatory or libellous;\n\n
    8.	infringes upon or violates any third party\'s rights [including, but not limited to, intellectual property rights, rights of privacy (including without limitation unauthorized disclosure of a person\'s name, email address, physical address or phone number) or rights of publicity];\n\n
    9.	promotes an illegal or unauthorized copy of another person\'s copyrighted work, such as providing pirated computer programs or links to them, providing information to circumvent manufacture-installed copy-protect devices, or providing pirated music or links to pirated music files;\n\n
    10.	contains restricted or password-only access pages, or hidden pages or images (those not linked to or from another accessible page);\n\n
    11.	provides material that exploits people in a sexual, violent or otherwise inappropriate manner or solicits personal information from anyone;\n\n
    12.	provides instructional information about illegal activities such as making or buying illegal weapons, violating someone\'s privacy, or providing or creating computer viruses;\n\n
    13.	contains video, photographs, or images of another person (with a minor or an adult).\n\n
    14.	tries to gain unauthorized access or exceeds the scope of authorized access to the Platform or to profiles, blogs, communities, account information, bulletins, friend request, or other areas of the Platform or solicits passwords or personal identifying information for commercial or unlawful purposes from other users;\n\n
    15.	engages in commercial activities and/or sales without Our prior written consent such as contests, sweepstakes, barter, advertising and pyramid schemes, or the buying or selling of "virtual" products related to the Platform. Throughout this Terms of Use, Rashan Store\'s prior written consent means a communication coming from Rashan Store\'s Legal Department, specifically in response to Your request, and specifically addressing the activity or conduct for which You seek authorization;\n\n
    16.	solicits gambling or engages in any gambling activity which We, in Our sole discretion, believes is or could be construed as being illegal;\n\n
    17.	interferes with another User\'s use and enjoyment of the Platform or any other individual\'s User and enjoyment of similar services;\n\n
    18.	refers to any website or URL that, in Our sole discretion, contains material that is inappropriate for the Platform or any other website, contains content that would be prohibited or violates the letter or spirit of these Terms of Use.\n\n
    19.	harm minors in any way;\n\n
    20.	infringes any patent, trademark, copyright or other proprietary rights or third party\'s trade secrets or rights of publicity or privacy or shall not be fraudulent or involve the sale of counterfeit or stolen products;\n\n
    21.	violates any law for the time being in force;\n\n
    22.	deceives or misleads the addressee/ users about the origin of such messages or communicates any information which is grossly offensive or menacing in nature;\n\n
    23.	impersonate another person;\n\n
    24.	contains software viruses or any other computer code, files or programs designed to interrupt, destroy or limit the functionality of any computer resource; or contains any trojan horses, worms, time bombs, cancel-bots, easter eggs or other computer programming routines that may damage, detrimentally interfere with, diminish value of, surreptitiously intercept or expropriate any system, data or personal information;\n\n
    25.	threatens the unity, integrity, defence, security or sovereignty of India, friendly relations with foreign states, or public order or causes incitement to the commission of any cognizable offence or prevents investigation of any offence or is insulting any other nation.\n\n
    26.	shall not be false, inaccurate or misleading;\n\n
    27.	shall not, directly or indirectly, offer, attempt to offer, trade or attempt to trade in any item, the dealing of which is prohibited or restricted in any manner under the provisions of any applicable law, rule, regulation or guideline for the time being in force.\n\n
    28.	shall not create liability for Rashan Store or cause Rashan Store to lose (in whole or in part) the services of our internet service provider ("ISPs") or other suppliers;\n\n
    29.	You shall not use any "deep-link", "page-scrape", "robot", "spider" or other automatic device, program, algorithm or methodology, or any similar or equivalent manual process, to access, acquire, copy or monitor any portion of the Platform or any Content, or in any way reproduce or circumvent the navigational structure or presentation of the Platform or any Content, to obtain or attempt to obtain any materials, documents or information through any means not purposely made available through the Platform. Rashan Store reserve its right to bar any such activity.\n\n
    30.	User shall not attempt to gain unauthorized access to any portion or feature of the Platform, or any other systems or networks connected to the Platform or to any server, computer, network, or to any of the services offered on or through the Platform, by hacking, password "mining" or any other illegitimate means.\n\n
    31.	Unless expressly permitted, User shall not probe, scan or test the vulnerability of the Platform or any network connected to the Platform nor breach the security or authentication measures on the Platform or any network connected to the Platform. User may not reverse look-up, trace or seek to trace any information on any other User of or visitor to Platform, or any other user, including any account on the Platform not owned by User, to its source, or exploit the Platform or any service or information made available or offered by or through the Platform, in any way where the purpose is to reveal any information, including but not limited to personal identification or information, other than User’s own information, as provided for by the Platform.\n\n
    4.	User Accounts\n\n
    a.	User must be registered on the Platform to access or avail the Services. Except with Rashan Store’s approval, one User may only register one account on the Platform. Rashan Store may cancel or terminate a User’s account if Rashan Store has reasons to suspect that the User has concurrently registered or controlled two or more accounts. Further, Rashan Store may reject User’s application, without assigning any reasons thereof, for registration for any other reason.\n\n
    b.	A set of User ID and OTP (One Time Password) / password is unique to a single account. You shall be solely responsible for maintaining the confidentiality and security of your user ID and password and for all activities that occur under User’s account. You agree that all activities that occur under your account (including without limitation, posting any company or product information, clicking to accept any terms and conditions or rules, subscribing to or making any payment for any services, sending emails using the Platform or other communications) will be deemed to have been authorized by you.\n\n
    5.	User’s Responsibilities\n\n
    a.	You represents, warrants and agrees that (a) you are at least eighteen (18) years of age or above and are fully able and competent to understand and agree to the Terms (b) you have full power and authority to accept the Terms, to grant the license and authorization and to perform the obligations hereunder; © you use the Platform and Services for business purposes only; and (d) the address you provide when registering is the principal place of business of your business entity.\n\n
    b.	User will be required to provide information or material about User’s entity, business or products/services as part of the registration process on the Platform or your use of any Service or the User account.  Each User represents, warrants and agrees that (a) such information and material whether submitted during the registration process or thereafter throughout the continuation of the use of the Platform or Service is true, accurate, current and complete, and (b) User will maintain and promptly amend all information and material to keep it true, accurate, current and complete.\n\n
    c.	User consents to the inclusion of the contact information about User in Rashan Store’s database.\n\n
    d.	You represents, warrants and agrees that (a) you shall be solely responsible for obtaining all necessary third party licenses and permissions regarding any User Content that you submit, post or display; (b) any User Content that User submit, post or display does not infringe or violate any of the copyright, patent, trademark, trade name, trade secrets or any other personal or proprietary rights of any third party ("Third Party Rights”); (c) User have the right and authority to sell, trade, distribute or export or offer to sell, trade, distribute or export the products or services described in the User Content and such sale, trade, distribution or export or offer does not violate any Third Party Rights.\n\n
    6.	Breaches\n\n
    a.	Rashan Store reserves the right in its sole discretion, without intimation to the User, remove, modify or reject any User Content that User submit to, post or display on the Platform which Rashan Store reasonably believes is unlawful, violates the Terms, could subject Rashan Store or its affiliates to liability, or is otherwise found inappropriate in Rashan Store’s opinion.\n\n
    b.	If any User breaches any Terms, or if Rashan Store has reasonable grounds to believe that a User is in breach of any Terms, Rashan Store shall have the right to take such disciplinary actions as it deems appropriate, including without limitation: (i) suspending or terminating the User’s account and any and all accounts determined to be related to such account by Rashan Store in its discretion; (ii) restricting, downgrading, suspending or terminating the subscription of, access to, or current or future use of any Service; (iii) removing any product listings or other User Content that the User has submitted, posted or displayed; and (v) any other corrective actions, discipline or penalties as Rashan Store may deem necessary or appropriate in its sole discretion.\n\n
    c.	Rashan Store reserves the right to cooperate fully with governmental authorities, private investigators and/or injured third parties in the investigation of any suspected criminal or civil wrongdoing.  Further, Rashan Store may disclose the User\'s identity and contact information, if requested by a government or law enforcement body, an injured third party, or as a result of a subpoena or other legal action.\n\n
    d.	Each User agrees to indemnify Rashan Store, its affiliates, directors, employees, agents and representatives and to hold them harmless, from any and all damages, losses, claims and liabilities (including legal costs on a full indemnity basis) which may arise from your submission, posting or display of any User Content, from your use of the Platform or Services, or from your breach of the Terms.\n\n
    7.	Transactions Between Users\n\n
    a.	For any Services, Rashan Store does not represent either the seller or the buyer in specific transactions. Rashan Store does not control and is not liable to or responsible for the quality, safety, lawfulness or availability of the products or services offered for sale on the Platform or the ability of the sellers to complete a sale or the ability of buyers to complete a purchase.\n\n
    b.	Users agree that Rashan Store cannot and does not confirm each User\'s purported identity. Rashan Store encourage Users to exercise discretion and caution while dealing with various Users.\n\n
    c.	Each User acknowledges that it is fully assuming the risks of conducting any purchase and sale transactions (hereinafter referred to as "Transaction Risk”) in connection with using the Platform or Services, and that it is fully assuming the risks of liability or harm of any kind in connection with subsequent activity of any kind relating to products or services that are the subject of transactions using the Platform.\n\n
    d.	In the event that any User has a dispute with any party to a transaction, such User agrees to release and indemnify Rashan Store (and our agents, affiliates, directors, officers and employees) from all claims, demands, actions, proceedings, costs, expenses and damages (including without limitation any actual, special, incidental or consequential damages) arising out of or in connection with such transaction. This clause shall also apply to any additional services opted for by the User by accessing any link from Rashan Store site to avail of services related to the transaction of buy-sell conducted on the Rashan Store Platform.\n\n
    8.	Limitation of Liability\n\n
    a.	TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, THE SERVICES PROVIDED BY RASHAN STORE ON OR THROUGH THE PLATFORM ARE PROVIDED "AS IS", "AS AVAILABLE" AND "WITH ALL FAULTS”, AND RASHAN STORE HEREBY EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ANY AND ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO, ANY WARRANTIES OF CONDITION, QUALITY, DURABILITY, PERFORMANCE, ACCURACY, RELIABILITY, MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. ALL SUCH WARRANTIES, REPRESENTATIONS, CONDITIONS, AND UNDERTAKINGS ARE HEREBY EXCLUDED.\n\n
    b.	TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, RASHAN STORE MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES ABOUT THE VALIDITY, ACCURACY, CORRECTNESS, RELIABILITY, QUALITY, STABILITY, COMPLETENESS OR CURRENTNESS OF ANY INFORMATION PROVIDED ON OR THROUGH THE PLATFORM; RASHAN STORE DOES NOT REPRESENT OR WARRANT THAT THE MANUFACTURE, IMPORTATION, EXPORT, DISTRIBUTION, OFFER, DISPLAY, PURCHASE, SALE AND/OR USE OF PRODUCTS OR SERVICES OFFERED OR DISPLAYED ON THE PLATFORM DOES NOT VIOLATE ANY THIRD PARTY RIGHTS; AND RASHAN STORE MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND CONCERNING ANY PRODUCT OR SERVICE OFFERED OR DISPLAYED ON THE PLATFORM.\n\n
    9.	Force Majeure\n\n
    a.	Under no circumstances shall Rashan Store be held liable for any delay or failure or disruption of the content or services delivered through the Platform resulting directly or indirectly from acts of nature, forces or causes beyond our reasonable control, including without limitation, Internet failures, computer, telecommunications or any other equipment failures, electrical power failures, strikes, labor disputes, riots, insurrections, civil disturbances, shortages of labor or materials, fires, flood, storms, explosions, acts of God, war, governmental actions, orders of domestic or foreign courts or tribunals or non-performance of third parties.\n\n
    10.	Intellectual Property Rights\n\n
    a.	Rashan Store is the sole owner or lawful licensee of all the rights and interests in the Platform and the Platform Content. All title, ownership and intellectual property rights in the Platform and Platform Content shall remain with Rashan Store or licensors of the Platform Content, as the case may be. All rights not otherwise claimed under the Terms or by Rashan Store are hereby reserved.\n\n
    b.	"Rashan Store" and any other related icons and logos are registered trademarks or trademarks or service marks of Hiveloop Technology Private Limited, in various jurisdictions and are protected under applicable copyright, trademark and other proprietary rights laws. The unauthorized copying, modification, use or publication of these marks is strictly prohibited.\n\n
    11.	Notices\n\n
    a.	All legal notices or demands to or upon Rashan Store shall be made in writing and sent to Rashan Store personally, by courier, certified mail, or facsimile to the following entity and address: Hiveloop Technology Private Limited, 1090 G, 18thCross, 14th Main, Sector 3, HSR Layout, Bangalore - 560102, Attn: Legal Department. The notices shall be effective when they are received by Rashan Store in any of the above-mentioned manner.\n\n
    b.	All legal notices or demands to or upon a User shall be effective if either delivered personally, sent by courier, certified mail, by facsimile or email to the last-known correspondence, fax or email address provided by the User to Rashan Store, or by posting such notice or demand on an area of the Platform that is publicly accessible without a charge. Notice to a User shall be deemed to be received by such User if and when, a) Rashan Store is able to demonstrate that communication, whether in physical or electronic form, has been sent to such User, or b) immediately upon Rashan Store posting such notice on an area of the Platform that is publicly accessible without charge.\n\n
    12.	General Provisions\n\n
    a.	Subject to any terms and conditions, the Terms constitute the entire agreement between User and Rashan Store with respect to and govern User’s use of the Platform and Services, superseding any prior written or oral agreements in relation to the same subject matter herein.\n\n
    b.	Rashan Store and User are independent contractors, and no agency, partnership, joint venture, employee-employer relationship is intended or created by the Terms.\n\n
    c.	If any provision of the Terms is held to be invalid or unenforceable, such provision shall be deleted and the remaining provisions shall remain valid and be enforced.\n\n
    d.	Rashan Store’s failure to enforce any right or failure to act with respect to any breach by User under the Terms will not constitute a waiver of that right nor a waiver of Rashan Store’s right to act with respect to subsequent or similar breaches.\n\n
    e.	Rashan Store shall have the right to assign the Terms (including all of our rights, titles, benefits, interests, and obligations and duties in the Terms to any person or entity (including any affiliates of Rashan Store). User may not assign, in whole or part, the Terms to any person or entity.\n\n
    f.	The Terms shall be governed by the laws of India and the parties to the Terms agree to submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of Bangalore, Karnataka, India.\n\n
    13.	Grievance Officer\n\n
    In accordance with Information Technology Act 2000 and rules made there under, the name and contact details of the Grievance Officer are provided below:\n\n
    Sachin Kumar B\n\n
    Customer Service\n\n
    No. 1090 G, 18th Cross, 14th Main,\n\n
    Sector 3, HSR Layout, Bangalore – 560102.\n\n
    Phone: +91-9686976427\n\n
    Email:grievance-officer@Rashan Store.in\n\n
    Time: Mon - Sat (10:00 AM - 07:00 PM)\n\n
    IP Infringement Policy\n\n
    Notice and Procedure for Making Claims of Right Infringements\n\n
    We respect third parties Intellectual Property Rights. If your rights are being infringed, you notify us by submitting the Notice Form attached to this policy\n\n
    Upon receipt of a Notice Form we may take certain actions, such as informing the users about the infringing content or removing information without any admission as to liability and without prejudice to any rights, remedies or defenses, all of which are expressly reserved. Furthermore, in submitting a Notice Form, you grant to Rashan Store the right to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, create derivative works from, and display its content throughout the world in any media. This includes forwarding the Notice Form to the parties involved in the provision of the allegedly infringing content. You agree to indemnify Rashan Store for all claims brought by a third party against Rashan Store arising out of or in connection with the submission of a Notice Form.\n\n
    Note on Third Party User Listings: Please keep in mind that Third Party User listings are merely hosted on Rashan Store and are posted solely by the Third Party Users who may be contacted via their "User Information" page, accessible from any of their listings.\n\n
    Important Warning: giving false, misleading or inaccurate information in the Notice Form to Rashan Store may result in civil and/or criminal liability. You should contact a legal advisor should you have any questions.\n\n
    Notice Form:\n\n
    If you believe that your rights are being violated by an information on the Rashan Store, you may fill out and submit the Notice Form (below). This form needs to be signed can be sent via E-mail PDF to the Grievance Officer:\n\n
    e-mail: infringement@Rashan Store.in\n\n
    Subject Line: Notice of Infringement\n\n
    (We will accept a signed PDF via e-mail with the subject line "Notice of Infringement").\n\n
    Please fill out the Notice form using the corresponding numbered paragraphs to frame your communication.\n\n
    Notice Form\n\n
    I, [INSERT FULL NAME AND TITLE] of [COMPANY NAME, IF APPLICABLE], state as follows:\n\n
    1.	Contact information\n\n
    (a) Your and/ or your company\'s name, address, telephone number and contact email address; (b)The contact email address and/or name which we will provide to Third Party Sellers (if relevant) so they may contact you to resolve any issues regarding your notification to us. If you do not provide a separate contact email, you authorize us to use the contact information you provide in while registering at Rashan Store.\n\n
    2.	Listing\'s details and Allegation of Infringed Right:\n\n
    (a) The listing\'s URL and detailed description of the information that you claim is infringing your rights is located on Rashan Store Platform; if regarding a Third Party User listing please also provide the name used to identify the User on the Platform. (b) A description of your intellectual property right(s) that you claim has/have been infringed. Please provide the copy of Trademark Certificate / Copyright Registration Certificate / Patent Registration Certificate.  [Please also provide as to how you have arrived in determining that third party Intellectual Property Rights have been infringed]\n\n
    3.	Include the following statement: "I have a good faith belief that the portion of the listing(s) described above violate(s) the intellectual property rights owned by the intellectual property owner or its agent, nor is such use otherwise permissible under law." [Please provide a copy of authorization Certificate in favour of applicant]\n\n
    4.	Include the following statement: "I represent that the information in this notification is true and correct and that I am the intellectual property owner or authorised to act on behalf of the intellectual property owner for the rights described above."\n\n
    5.	Sign the Notice Form.
</string>
    <string name="title_activity_my_products">MyProducts</string>
    <string name="title_activity_my_orders">MyOrders</string>
</resources>
